Deepak HN

Software Engineer

Address Bengaluru, Karnataka, 520010

Phone +91-7829542986

E-mail deepu.rrr@gmail.com

WWW https://fflickit.wordpress.com/ **LinkedIn** www.linkedin.com/in/deepak-hn-b09ba283

Worked in domains such as ERP, Education. Designed and developed Microsoft technology-related applications from scratch. Gathered and consolidated requirements from different teams and clients. Developed executables, web portals, designed database schemas, and tables. A team player focused on achieving project objectives with speed and accuracy.

Skills

C, **C#**, **MSSqI**, **MYSqI**, ASP.NET, **ASP.NET CORE**, **MVC**, **Ajax**, VB.NET, **Web API**, Bootstrap, MVVM, MVP, XML, HTML5, XAML, CSS, JavaScript, **jQuery**, **Azure WebApps**, Visual Studio, JMeter

Team Foundation Service (TFS).

Understanding customer requirements.

Frontend design.

RDLC report designing using Visual Studio.

Testing and maintenance

Database programming

Troubleshooting, Performance Tuning

Data collection and analysis

Product development, Software Development

Typescript, Angular

Build Releases, Code Reviews

Azure Cloud Services, Solution Deployment

Work History

2018-02 - Current

Software Engineer

MeritTrac, Bengaluru, India

- Reporting Web Application: A web application to retrieve relevant data.
 Technologies Used: MVC, EntityFrameworkCore, Membership Db, ASP.NET Core, Ajax, jQuery, jQuery Datatable, Bootstrap.
- **AFIS Fingerprint match**: A tool, using AFIS algorithm to find potential matches of vast amount of fingerprint data to find duplicate logins or test taking.

- Safe Exam Browser: Safe exam browser is a tool to conduct online exam by locking users screen with browser in kiosk mode by disabling Bluetooth, WIFI connections, Firewall and whitelisting only specific URLs which loads test player where user takes online test/exam. Console Application
- Online Test Booking System(OTBS): Product is to book a seat for any university level test. Booking is made real time so candidate is given 60 seconds to confirm booking. Web Application
- Authentrac and Bioentrac: Candidates are registered through Authentrac web application. User logs in to Bioentrac windows application to capture candidates photo and fingerprint image and data through webcam and biometric device which is a registration process and same is verified when the candidates come for second session of examination. Web and Winform
- **Registration System:** This system is used to capture fingerprint image and data of candidate using QR code scan. A random IP (system) is assigned while registering for taking an online test with respective system. *Winform*
- Online Exam Booking System(OEBS): Product is to book a seat for any university level exam. Web Application

2017-02 - 2018-02 Associate Software Engineer

Equax Software Labs, Bengaluru, India

- Business Occupation Management System (BOS) ERP Application: The Project is to maintain the business organization. ERP application predicts & balances demand & supply. Involves several modules such as Account, Sales & Purchase, Material.
- Forecasting & Bill Tracking System(FBTS): FBTS is designed and developed specifically to WIPRO GE HEALTHCARE. It is used to keep track FR,SR,BO and ST status on FR/s and SR/s used by WIPRO GE, their FR/s status from field request to part blocking with ordering team users and Stock Transfer & Back Order with ordering and GPOS/C09/X-ray team users and their SR/s status from verification to tracking of all the teams working on SR.

2014-09 - 2017-02 Associate Software Engineer - Trainee

Prerana IT Consultants, Bengaluru, India

- **HR and Payroll**: HR is the Payroll System that provides an up-to-date information to an organization's revitalized HR department on their employee base to focus on areas like successive planning, manpower and salary planning, intensive time management and so on. Includes employee details with his grades, designation, employee earnings and deductions using parameters, leave master, payslip generation.
- Business Occupation Management System (BOS) ERP Application: The Project is to maintain the business organization. ERP application predicts & balances demand & supply. Involves several modules such as Account, Sales & Purchase, Material.

Accomplishments

- Rewarded with **spot award** for managing multiple deliveries in a short time.
- Rewarded with spot award for successful application development and execution.
- Rewarded with spot award for successful application development and execution.

Education

2009-05 - 2013-05 Bachelor of Technology: Computer Science

CIT

Bachelors Degree [B.E], CIT, affiliated to Visvesvaraya Technological University

2005-07 - 2007-07 High School Diploma

Don Bosco High School

Blogging, Trekking, Logo Creation

I review on movies mostly non-mainstream, have a fondness towards travel, trekking and camping, and also creating logos, writing small scripts are part of my free time activity.